

CONTACT

- **** 09396594909
- clifforddanesyaun@gmail.com
- Sto. Tomas, Davao del Norte
- https://danesyeun.github.i o/danes-portfolio/

EDUCATION

2018 - 2023 UNIVERSITY OF IMMACULATE CONCEPTION

• BS in Computer Engineering

2016 - 2018 ATENEO DE DAVAO UNIVERSITY

• STEM - Pre Computer Studies

SKILLS

- SQL (MySQL)
- Javascript (ReactJS, Vanilla JavaScript, jQuery)
- HTML & CSS
- PHP (Laravel)
- C#
- Bootstrap
- Git

CLIFFORD DANES YAUN COMPUTER ENGINEER

PROFILE

I'm a Computer Engineering graduate with a background in software development, having worked with C#, ReactJS, and PostgreSQL. I currently manage several applications, including web and desktop apps, as well as Windows services for our HR and finance systems. I'm driven by tech challenges and enjoy optimizing and maintaining diverse software solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CoreDev Solutions Inc.

2024 - PRESENT

Software Engineer

- Developed and maintained an online membership application for the clients using Laravel and Bootstrap.
- Maintained and developed a mobile collector application and APIs.
- Maintained a Bank Reconciliation Desktop Application for client transactions.
- Developed and maintained a biometric time in/out windows service.

CoreDev Solutions Inc.

2023 - 2024

Software Implementer

- Tested websites provided by the developer for bugs using SeleniumIDE.
- Monitor and supported clients that are using the company product.
- Installed Linux servers and company product to clients and performed port forwarding.
- Performed and created SQL queries for client customized reports.

Netzon Global Technologies Inc.

February - May 2023

Intern Software Developer

- Developed a Human Resource Information System (HRIS) for the company using C# and React.
- Designed some of the webpages using Figma.
- Developed and tested RESTful API per module for the back-end, and implemented webpages for the front-end. Also, integrated front-end to back-end API.